Guide to the Fashion Moda Archive MSS.091
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Material, 112471
  - Subseries F[8]: Slides, 112530
    - Neal, Willie, undated; cuid9428; 112559 (Box 14, Folder 128A.)
    - Paddock, Laura, undated; cuid9429; 112558 (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - Pink, Lady, undated; cuid9430; 112557 (Box 14, Folder 129A.)
    - Quinn, Barbara., undated; cuid9431; 112556 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - Reccha, Lewis., undated; cuid9432; 112555 (Box 14, Folder 131)
    - Rivera, James., undated; cuid9433; 112554 (Box 14, Folder 132)
    - Rifka, Judy, undated; cuid9434; 112553 (Box 14, Folder 132A.)
    - Roloff, Stephan., undated; cuid9435; 112552 (Box 14, Folder 133)
    - Rothchild, Gail., undated; cuid9436; 112551 (Box 14, Folder 134)
    - Schlefer, R., undated; cuid9437; 112550 (Box 14, Folder 135)
    - Schwartz, Steve, undated; cuid9438; 112549 (Box 14, Folder 136)
    - Seeno, Anson, undated; cuid9439; 112548 (Box 14, Folder 136A.)
    - Smith, Mary Agnes, undated; cuid9440; 112547 (Box 14, Folder 136B.)
    - Spero, Nancy., undated; cuid9441; 112546 (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - Steckel, Anita, undated; cuid9442; 112545 (Box 14, Folder 137A.)
    - Strauss, Sandy., undated; cuid9443; 112544 (Box 14, Folder 138)
    - Street Art, undated; cuid9444; 112543 (Box 14, Folder 138A.)
    - Spank., undated; cuid9445; 112542 (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - Sumner, Holly & Talbot, Nina., undated; cuid9446; 112541 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - Toral, Tabo., undated; cuid9447; 112540 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - Transue, Michael., undated; cuid9448; 112539 (Box 14, Folder 141A.)
    - Tuck, Norman., undated; cuid9449; 112538 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Unidentified artists, undated; cuid9450; 112537 (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - Various., undated; cuid9451; 112536 (Box 14, Folder 143A)
    - Warren, Tom, undated; cuid9452; 112535 (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Weeks, Lionel "Agent", undated; cuid9453; 112534 (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - Wodiczko, Krysztof., undated; cuid9454; 112533 (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Wosk, Miriam., undated; cuid9455; 112532 (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - undated, cuid9456; 112531 (Box 14, Folder .)
  - Subseries F[9]: Slides, 112528
    Box 15: Slide Presentation
    - Fashion Moda Slide Show: with explanation sheet (ca 1990), an introductory overview, including certain duplicates, cuid9457; 112529 (Box 15, Folder 148)
  - Subseries G: Video - Access Copies, 112505
    Consists of VHS access copies for Stephan Eins' Making Coincidences and other cable TV programs. Access copies are listed chronologically.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - Cable TV 1 - Josef, circa mid-1970s; ID: 091.0071; 112527 (Case 091.0071)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Duration: 00:29:00.
    - Cable TV 2 - Leanne, circa mid-1970s; ID: 091.0073; 112526 (Case 091.0073)
    - Cable TV 3 - Terry & Wendy, circa mid-1970s; ID: 091.0075; 112525 (Case 091.0075)
    - Cable TV 4 - Alone, circa mid-1970s; ID: 091.0078; 164999 (Case 091.0078)
      Format: DVD
      Duration: 00:29:00
    - "Grafitti" Dub; CBS "30-Minutes", undated; ID: 091.0081; 165000 (Case 091.0081)
      Duration: 00:14:00
    - Making Coincidences, February 5, 1984., ID: 091.0033; 112524 (Case 091.0033)
    - Making Coincidences, February 12, 1984, ID: 091.0035; 112523 (Case 091.0035)
    - Making Coincidences, February 19, 1984, ID: 091.0037; 112522 (Case 091.0037)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Duration: 00:30:00.
    - Making Coincidences, February 26, 1984, ID: 091.0039; 112521 (Case 091.0039)
    - Making Coincidences, March 4, 1984, ID: 091.0041; 112520 (Case 091.0041)
    - Making Coincidences, March 18, 1984, ID: 091.0043; 112519 (Case 091.0043)
    - Making Coincidences, March 25, 1984, ID: 091.0045; 112518 (Case 091.0045)
    - Making Coincidences, April 1, 1984, ID: 091.0047; 112517 (Case 091.0047)
    - Making Coincidences, April 8, 1984, ID: 091.0049; 112516 (Case 091.0049)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Duration: 00:28:00.
    - Making Coincidences, April 15, 1984 (as per cassette)/April 22, 1984 (as per container), ID: 091.0051; 112515 (Case 091.0051)
    - Making Coincidences, April 29 & May 6, 1984, ID: 091.0053; 112514 (Case 091.0053)
    - Making Coincidences, May 13, 1984, ID: 091.0055; 112513 (Case 091.0055)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984, ID: 091.0057; 112512 (Case 091.0057)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984, ID: 091.0059; 112511 (Case 091.0059)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Duration: 00:07:00.
    - Making Coincidences, June 3, 1984, ID: 091.0061; 112510 (Case 091.0061)
    - Making Coincidences, X. Y. C., 1984; ID: 091.0063; 112509 (Case 091.0063)
    - Slow Scan: March, 1979, ID: 091.0084; 165001 (Case 091.0084)
      Duration: 00:22:00
    - Stefan Eins Presents: July 11 and 21, 1986, ID: 091.0065; 112508 (Case 091.0065)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: 2/25/1987, ID: 091.0067; 112507 (Case 091.0067)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Duration: 00:47:00.
    - Stefan Eins Presents: edit in process, March 25, 1987, ID: 091.0069; 112506 (Case 091.0069)
  - Subseries H: Video - Originals, 112472
    Consists of original source tapes for Stephan Eins' Making Coincidences and other cable TV programs. Materials are listed chronologically. For access copies please see Subseries G.
    - Press for Making Coincidences, title cards for show. [see also oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9458; 112504 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Cable TV-1-Josef, n. d., circa mid-1970s; cuid9459; 112503 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0021)
      3/4" Umatic videocassette. Tape length 30 minutes.
    - Cable TV -2-Leanne, n. d., circa mid-1970s; cuid9460; 112502 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0022)
    - Cable TV -3-Terry & Wendy, n. d., circa mid-1970s; cuid9461; 112501 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0023)
    - Cable TV -4-Alone, n. d., circa mid-1970s; cuid9462; 112500 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0024)
    - [1.] -- Slow Scan Tele Conference [2.] -- Manhattan/Bronx; 3/6/1979 and 3/7/1979., cuid9463; 112499 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0029)
      3/4" Umatic videocassette. Tape length 20 minutes.
    - Fashion Moda Documentary, July 4, 1982., cuid9464; 112498 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0026)
      1/2" VHS videocassette PAL. Tape length 120 minutes.
    - Making Coincidences, February 5, 1984., cuid9465; 112497 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0001)
    - Making Coincidences, February 12, 1984., cuid9466; 112496 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0002)
    - Making Coincidences, February 19, 1984., cuid9467; 112495 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0003)
    - Making Coincidences, February 26, 1984., cuid9468; 112494 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0004)
    - Making Coincidences, March 4, 1984., cuid9469; 112493 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0005)
    - Making Coincidences, March 18, 1984., cuid9470; 112492 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0006)
    - Making Coincidences, March 25, 1984., cuid9471; 112491 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0007)
    - Making Coincidences, April 1, 1984., cuid9472; 112490 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0008)
    - Making Coincidences, April 8, 1984., cuid9473; 112489 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0009)
    - Making Coincidences, April 15, 1984 (as per cassette)/April 22, 1984 (as per container)., cuid9474; 112488 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0010)
    - Making Coincidences, April 29 & May 6, 1984., cuid9475; 112487 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0011)
    - Making Coincidences, May 13, 1984., cuid9476; 112486 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0012)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984., cuid9477; 112485 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0013)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984., cuid9478; 112484 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0014)
    - Making Coincidences, June 3, 1984., cuid9479; 112483 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0015)
    - Making Coincidences, X. Y. C., n. d.., 1984; cuid9480; 112482 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0016)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: July 11 and 21, 1986., cuid9481; 112481 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0017)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: 2/25/1987., cuid9482; 112480 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0018)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: edit in process, March 25, 1987., cuid9483; 112479 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0019)
    - Commercials for Stefan, n. d., 1987; cuid9484; 112478 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0020)
    - Colab extinction, n. d., undated; cuid9485; 112477 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0025)
      Betamax
    - Fashion Moda Gallery- South Bronx, tape 1., undated; cuid9486; 112476 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0027)
    - Graffiti., undated; cuid9487; 112475 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0028)
    - Barbara Smith Fashion Moda Request E., undated; cuid9488; 112474 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0030)
      1/2" VHS videocassette PAL. Tape length 30 minutes.
    - Unidentified video tape., undated; cuid9489; 112473 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0031)
- Oversize: Series II: Fashion Moda as a Business, 112465
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files, 112466
    - Ongoing renovations., undated; cuid9490; 112467 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Oversize: Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Materials, 112427
  - Subseries A: Artist Files, 112456
    - Science, Invention, Technology, Art and Fantasy, images used for first exhibition, 1978 [see also I. 1. 7A], cuid9492; 112463 (Box 22, Folder 3 - 3.2)
    - "Science, Invention, Technology, Art and Fantasy", production material 1978 [see also I. 1. 7A], cuid9493; 112462 (Box 22, Folder 2 - 2.1)
    - Designs for Documenta 7 t-shirts, 1982. [No Duplication Allowed], cuid9494; 112461 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Holzer, Jenny: "Truisms", for Documenta 7, 1982.[No Duplication Allowed], cuid9495; 112460 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Production Materials for Documenta 7 Store, 1982.[No Duplication Allowed], cuid9496; 112459 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Production Materials for Documenta 7, transparencies. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9497; 112458 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Science, Art, Design, Invention, Technology, Fantasy, a brochure, 1984, cuid9498; 112457 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries B: Exhibition Promotion., 112448
    - Flyers and Posters, 1979- 1981; cuid9499; 112455 (Box 24, Folder 12 - 12.1)
    - Flyers and Posters, 1983- 1988; cuid9500; 112454 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Flyers and Posters, 1989- 1993; cuid9501; 112453 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Flyers and Posters, n. d., undated; cuid9502; 112452 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1981; cuid9503; 112451 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, n. d., undated; cuid9504; 112450 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Announcements from other galleries., undated; cuid9505; 112449 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries C: Photographs., 112446
    - Eins, Stefan, Jones, Baird & Mark Kostabi, 1985- 1986; cuid9506; 112447 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries D: Artworks., 112430
    - Aone, painting. (tag) [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9507; 112445 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Crash, painting. (tag) [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9508; 112444 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Eins, Stefan: painting (tag, drawing), undated; cuid9509; 112443 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Fekner, John: drawing for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9510; 112442 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Haring, Keith: drawing for Documenta 7.[No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9511; 112441 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Mullican Matt: poster, undated; cuid9512; 112440 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Nenner, Paulette: drawing. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9513; 112439 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Pou, Alyson: collage. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9514; 112438 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Scharf, Kenny: drawings for Documenta 7.[No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9515; 112437 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Toxic, drawing. (tag), undated; cuid9516; 112436 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - G-Man, Tag, undated; cuid9517; 112435 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - van Dalen, Anton: drawing for Documenta 7 [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9518; 112434 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Wells, David: drawing for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9519; 112433 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Y-Pants, drawing, undated; cuid9520; 112432 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - unidentified drawing, undated; cuid9521; 112431 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries H: Video - Originals, 112428
    Subseries H: Video - Originals
    Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available.
    - Making Coincidences, title cards., undated; cuid9522; 112429 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Over-Oversize: Series I: Fashion Moda Overview, 112424
  - Cooney, Robert "Por Exxon, for Kill", painting., undated; cuid9523; 112426 (Flat-file-folder 30)
  - Eins, Stefan "Billiard/Pool for Random Objects", instructions., undated; cuid9524; 112425 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Over-Oversize: Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Materials, 112415
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files, 112421
    - Eins, Stefan: poster., undated; cuid9525; 112423 (Flat-file-folder 32)
    - Evans, Andrea: proposal., undated; cuid9526; 112422 (Box 20)
  - Subseries B: Grants and Fundraising, 112419
    - flyers and poster, 1983-1987; cuid9527; 112420 (Flat-file-folder 33)
  - Subseries D: Artworks, 112416
    - Kostner, Arthur: two drawings., undated; cuid9528; 112418 (Flat-file-folder 31)
    - Fashion Moda Portfolio., undated; cuid9529; 112417 (Folder 8)